Wow!
How did you do this?
I created it from spirit force taken from you
and material sprites I stocked up.
This is creation magic, right?
How can I control it?
It's your spirit force.
You should know better.
How will you use it?
It'll be the bait.
We can't leave this space even if it was open,
unless they take us out.
And you must retrieve the copy,
or you lose cultivation.
I know.
So we'll let them believe we can leave.
What's your plan?
I've got Muluo immortal's soul stone.
It's the same two as before.
Perfect.
Have you found it?
Yes.
It's time you kept your promise.
If it turns out they can sense us, we call it off.
Don't you think it's strange you can't see those three?
We revert behind the screen and come out.
Why do you say that?
So your closed eyes are just a facade.
I thought you rely on spirit sense.
He's a lock-up master.
It's unlikely he senses us.
Haven't you noticed they already left?
We draw his attention to the copy, and make him lose confidence.
None of you can leave this spirit space.
Don't be so sure about it.
None of you are space type.
How do you know we can't leave?
He's going to doubt himself.
Qiuxian.
Among them, only the old frog can sense spirit bodies.
So if they don't see you,
they will believe you aren't there.
We move the moment I retrieved the copy.
As fast as we can, we hide on him.
We will be so light,
he surely won't notice us.
Unless they discover us,
there's no way for the two of them
to tell we're still there.
Impossible...
Stay here and watch.
I call Polao in.
He controls this space.
Only he can bring people in and out.
We don't know where he takes us,
this can pose a risk.
Since they already found the Pearl,
they must be somewhere in the city.
The top of a building would be the best for us.
They'll be distracted while he's explaining the situation to the others.
They won't notice a rice-sized object falling.
We teleport before the space switch could be cut.
And that's when we escape.
So adorable!
So cute!
So kawaii!
Xiaohei, are you okay?
Should've stayed home...
What's happening?
I think it's your friend.
Escape and Battle
Didn't you say this space is infallible?
They must have abilities unknown to us.
Couldn't you be more careful?
The unknown is to be feared.
Even the strongest spirit space can't nullify every power.
I can't even imagine what ability could take them out of there.
I could have stayed to watch them.
What a bunch of promise breakers...
Remember, they aren't our objective.
Though we must act quickly.
As I thought, we're near the con.
What will be our next step?
I still remember you guys are after the Pearl.
You're frank.
We take our leave now.
We won't steal it?
It was fun working with you.
I hope next time we can have a good long talk.
Mr. Luo.
There's one more thing.
The Soul Calling Stone we gave you...
What about it?
In fact, we used it...
to sense your approximate location.
No wonder you found me.
We're sorry.
Enemies make the best friends.
I can remove the tracking.
But I still can use it to contact you, right?
Sure.
You tried in vain this time too.
Cultivation is never child's play.
I hope we'll meet again.
I'm sure we will.
Dammit!
You were awesome.
But you were even more so.
Shan Xin!
Xiaobai!
What are you doing?
It's a contest! I can win a limited edition game!
It looks like...
How come there's not a single place to hide...
If I just cross the road, they'll see me.
Had I known, I'd have brought my cell phone...
But I don't know Xiaobai's number...
They walk in plain sight?!
Are you sure this is safe?
I have observed the place.
It's some kind of masquerade.
If we keep a low profile,
no one will pay attention.
All right.
I think you were wrong!
- So lifelike!
- Which game is this?
What's happening?
Can we make some photos?
Diting?
Do I sense it wrong?
No.
"Double Deadly Alliance"?
But it's a two-player game.
Rules allow any console game, right?
And this is the one we're good at.
You can choose a partner.
Xiaobai, can you play that?
I can walk back and forth.
Better than nothing.
What about Xiaohei?
Are you serious?
I'll play with you.
But there's only one prize.
I don't need the prize.
But it wouldn't be fair to you.
I'd rather be with my friend.
If we lose, so what?
I love you, little girl!
I didn't mean it like that, sir...!
I'll play.
But I'm not that good.
I've never won.
No problem! Come!
Not so glorious to win like that, huh?
We'll still do our best!
Your controllers disconnected?
Directed by:
Mutou
Character design:
Biti
Key animation:
Gen
Kali
Bobo
Dongdong
Silly Tail (Dai Wei)
Animation:
Rou Shan
Shuai Hu
Yezi
Haozi
Jiu Jiu
Wen Tao
Youzi
Backgrounds:
Mang Yan
Qi Feng
Mao Zha
Modeling:
Da Shuang
Lulu
Da Huang
Kui Zhi
Little Fish (Xiao Yu)
Design:
Fenmo
Dandan
Service staff:
Huniu
Tu Bei
Tu Yi
Kucha
Xiaobai, Shan Xin,
Xiaohei, Gen:
Shan Xin
Diting:
Huang Zhenji
Musi, Axian, Tanjiu:
Ding Dang
Qingqiu:
Teng Xin
Fu, Polao, Gamer Guy:
Tutehameng
Shujiang:
Youwu Yueshan
Hanwu:
Li Lanling
Sound engineer:
Sound:
Sun Yujing
Xu Wei
Bohe
Wang Miao
This didn't work.
It looks like a lot of humans like me...
Diting!
Xuanli?
Wait for them to come out?
We can't.
We must wrap this up soon.
Polao.
Please go in for them.
Going in I certainly can,
but I have no ability to sense the Sky Pearl.
They haven't moved for a while.
They are in the southeast corner.
A black cat.
Must be easy to find.
Southeast corner...
I can indeed feel spirit aura there.
All right then.
I will wait for the opportunity.
Thank you.
We leave it to you, old frog.
Old frog?
He's already gone.
Unwritten Rule
That must be him.
Diting?!
He must have heard me...
Why doesn't he answer?
What are you doing here?
Haven't you met Xiaobai?
I'm with her.
Really? Thank goodness!
Some spirits are looking for them.
They are already here.
Gen, my friend.
You left without a word.
Don't you want to keep your promise?
I said I'd tell him to give it to you.
Xiaohei, give it to them.
Hell no.
You're angry only because I could escape.
Don't you think it was rather impolite?
Was locking me up a polite thing to do?
Anyone who possesses the prize of a vow quest, must bear the risk of robbery.
It's an unwritten rule of vow quests.
How is this an unwritten rule?
It's just that Laozi won't intervene.
Everyone knows he can't deal with events on Earth.
When some people started to say this, the others accepted it as a rule.
In the end, you're just looking for a reason to justify robbery.
Or do you really think this is fair?
Why didn't you say so yesterday?
You would've beaten me.
Aren't you afraid now of getting hurt?
Now I've got Diting.
Lord Diting can't get involved with the Pearl, I'm afraid.
It's true.
If he does, I'll give him a hard time!
Fu!
Behave yourself.
Stupid old frog!
Don't act like you're the boss!
This so-called Diting, maybe he's a fake!
Fu!
I'm burning up!
Please excuse him.
The Sky Pearl!
Why do you need it?
No need for you to know.
What if I don't give it up?
Then we'll take it by force.
And what if the moment you attack,
I give it to Diting?
What good would it make to you?
If I can't keep it,
I feel better if you feel bad.
Do you think I won't do it?
You two made up this scheme!
I didn't know about this.
But I certainly wouldn't mind to retrieve the Pearl.
I give you my word,
that if I get the Pearl, I won't give it to him again.
Qingqiu.
We'd better tell them.
Please forgive us...
We don't accept prize robbery as a rule either.
The truth is...
we didn't wish to do it like this.
But we need the Pearl so much,
we would give anything for it.
Is it possible you're willing to part with it?
What for?
To save our friend's life.
Really?
Come on, kid! Why should we lie to you now?
It smells nice.
Sassy brat! Do you want me to eat you?
He isn't lying.
How do you know?
To avoid being deceived, Master Lao lent me the Mind-Discerning Mirror.
How convenient.
Just give it to them.
If it was that simple, we wouldn't have done all this!
Do have any idea what it is for?
Easy to say so.
This is...
Do you really give it to us?
You should have said so earlier.
But...
It's the Sky Pearl! The hell thought you'd just give it away!
Don't you know what it can do?!
You can give it back.
Shame on us...
We humbly accept the Pearl.
If you are ever in need of our help,
just inquire at the club hall.
We will be at your service.
We are brothers now!
Sweet!
I still hate you!
We wish to bring home the news right away.
We must say goodbye now.
Goodbye.
See ya later, little spirits!
They're clients of the club hall.
Couldn't Laozi have helped them?
If it was that simple,
the Pearl wouldn't have stayed at Master Lao for centuries.
Then how could Xiaohei take it?
With his ability.
And because he's strong.
Is he stronger even than Gen?
Before I wounded him,
he was stronger than Xuanli right now.
Not at all.
Right now?
I've said too much.
I'm going back to Master Lao.
Kitten.
You gave up the Pearl too easily.
I hope you won't regret it.
Did I say something wrong?
It's Xiaohei who made him angry.
After all, the Pearl has a special significance for him and Master Lao.
I've got to say...
You really gave it up easily.
They needed it more.
The Sky Pearl can heal illnesses?
Only one type of illness.
But that's not why spirits want it.
Then why do they want it?
What makes it so precious,
is that if an ordinary spirit gets it,
he can become an immortal.
Directed by:
Mutou
Key animation:
Gen
Kali
Dongdong
Dai Wei
Little Ficus (Xiao Rong)
Koukou
Chestnut (Lizi)
Character design:
Biti
Animation:
Rou Shan
Yezi
Jiu Jiu
Luo Yi
OZ
Shiyue
Big White (Da Bai)
Backgrounds:
Mang Yen
Qi Feng
Mao Zha
Modeling:
Da Shuang
Lulu
Da Huang
Kui Zhi
Little Fish (Xiao Yu)
Little Daylily (Xiao Xuan)
Design:
Fenmo
Dandan
Youzi
Service staff:
Hu Niu
Tu Bei
Tu Yi
Kucha
Xiaobai,
Xiaohei, Gen:
Shan Xin
Diting:
Huang Zhenji
Qingqiu, Qianzhen:
Teng Xin
Fu, Polao:
Tutehameng
Sound engineer:
Wu Wuwu
Piyu:
Tao Bao
Heishu:
Ai Suo
Sound:
Sun Yujing
Xu Wei
Pohe
Wang Miao
Immortal?
So...
It's basically a life elixir?
We can say that.
If it makes anyone an immortal,
aren't there many people who want it?
Because it's not that easy.
It's the hardest quest in the books of vows.
It's in Master Lao's realm,
protected by powerful barriers.
Actually, no one considers it a target.
Xiaohei, you're awesome!
In the case of Xiaohei,
if he's within a certain range,
barriers are as if they're not there.
That's right...
It's the perfect ability for stealing.
Don't be jealous...
And aren't there any very strong spirits who need it?
There are.
But those spirits
don't want to offend Master Lao.
After all it's just a game he made up to amuse himself.
So...
you just gave up on the chance to become an immortal?
I can't use it.
And it just brings trouble.
But why did all the trouble find me...?
Hmph.
I hoped for a bit of a fight.
Gen, why are you here?
Had something to do.
Did you win?
You bet!
Look!
So cool!
This is a console exclusive to the game.
Limited edition.
A 1000 were made.
A 1000 pieces?
Isn't that a lot?
You're still so clueless.
There were 10 million preorders on it.
And what's the difference?
I don't know either.
We'll know when the time comes.
The point is that I have it.
Xiaohei.
Can you give me the box from yesterday?
Where did you keep it??
I noticed that your box looks like mine.
Can you tell me what's this?
That's the limited edition too!
Where'd you get it?
It was a gift.
Cool.
Now that we both have it, we can play together.
You play Gate of the Living, too?
This is my player ID.
You can friend me.
Alrighty.
What are they doing at the door?
And they're pretty dirty too.
We're leaving now.
Okay.
Huang.
Say goodbye to Xiaohei.
Grandpa, we're back!
How come you're back only now?
Didn't you say you come yesterday?
It's a long story...
But I brought the money.
Early Morning
Crescent Moon
Why is this happening, right in the morning?!
Good morning.
Morning.
Directed by:
Mutou
Key animation:
Gen
Kali
Dongdong
Xiao Rong
Koukou
Lizi
Dai Wei
who was
left alone
Storyboard:
Mr. Ordinary
(Fanzi)
Animation:
Rou Shan
Yezi
Jiu Jiu
Luo Yi
OZ
Shiyue
Da Bai
Backgrounds:
Mang Yan
Qi Feng
Mao Zha
Modeling:
Da Shuang
Lulu
Kui Zhi
Xiao Yu
Xiao Xuan
Ribbit (Guagua)
Design:
Fenmo
Dandan
Youzi
Service staff:
Hu Niu
Tu Bei
Tu Yi
Kucha
Xiaobai, Shan Xin,
Xiaohei, Xiaohuang, Gen:
Shan Xin
Dongdong:
Ding Dang
Purple-haired Loli:
Yan Meme
Crowd:
Ding Dang
Mr. Ordinary (Fanzi)
Eye Sound (Tong Yin)
White Flood (Bai Miao)
Roadside Fern (Bian Wei)
Sound engineer:
Yan Huanhuan
Piyu:
Tao Bao
Heishu:
Ai Suo
Sound:
Sun Yujing
Xu Wei
Bohe
Wang Miao
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
Our destination may be whimsical
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
kore kara deau kimi e to
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Mochiyotta hako aketara
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Are so precious and so fleeting
Omoi wa kitto kienai
Those feelings will never fade away
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me